老爸好
Hey, dad.
你觉得我的新好市多卡上的照片怎么样
What do you think of the picture on my new Costco card?
你从没把脸靠得离我这么近过
Wow, you've never put your actual face that close to mine.
杰觉得...
Jay thinks that --
让他说
Let him answer.
看着不错
Okay, you look good.
跟我一点也不像
This looks nothing like me!
可能是因为照片里你没在大吼
Maybe 'cause you're not yelling in it.
我看到这个 心里想的是
I look at this, and I'm like,
"什么鬼 火花都去哪了"
"What the hell? Where's the sparkle?
那个触底得分 被队友高高抬起的
Where's the guy that scored the winning touchdown
家伙哪里去了
and was carried off by his team?"
这家伙像是被海浪拍死在沙滩上的
This guy looks like he was carried off by the current.
我有点想
I have half a mind
把这卡剪掉 再也不去那里了
to cut this up and never go back there.
你可以用我们买的八联包剪刀的
Maybe you can use one of the scissors
其中一把来剪
from the eight-pack that we bought.
杰 有感觉了吗
Hey, Jay, you feeling it?
准备好把球瓶都扳倒了吗
You ready to knock down some pins?
太好了
Oh, great.
又灰又皱 跟我的老脸一样
Gray and wrinkled, like my tired puss.
今晚是我的联赛决赛
It's my league finals,
杰同意来替补我们的明星保龄球手莫里斯
and Jay agreed to fill in for our star bowler, Maurice,
他腹股沟拉伤还没好
who's recovering from a groin pull.
是真的腹股沟拉伤
An actual groin pull,
不是什么火烧岛上的派对
not the party on fire island.
不知道 卡梅隆
I don't know, Cameron.
我今晚真的没什么手感
I'm -- I'm really not feeling it tonight.
那你最好现在就开始有感觉
Well, you better start feeling it soon.
我们必须要赢
We need to win
好气气那个自以为是的马丁·谢尔曼
so I can stick it to that smug Martin Sherman.
马丁·谢尔曼是谁
Who's Martin Sherman?
我的死对头而已
Only my archrival.
我以为你的死对头
I thought your rival
是那个唱圣诞颂歌的金发男
was that blond Christmas caroler.
不是 是他们学校的西语老师
No, it's the Spanish teacher at his school.
小卡有很多死对头
Well, C-Cam has lots of rivals,
特别是如果算上那个扛包小伙的话
especially if you count that bag boy.
我跟你说过 别提他的名字
I told you -- never say his name.
我没提他的名字 我都不知道他叫什么
I didn't say his name. I don't even know his name.
他叫陶德
It's Todd.
老是把我的罐装食物放在蔬果上面
Always putting my canned goods on top of my produce.
真想把他的南瓜压扁
I'd like to squash his squash.
好了 走吧
Okay, let's go.
顺利的话 我们今晚不会很晚回来
Hopefully, we won't be out too late tonight.
我们会的
We will!
对了
Oh, yeah, right.
赌10块钱 你们会比我们先躺床上
$10 says you guys will be home in bed before we are.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
到时候你俩会睡觉
You two will be sleeping,
歌洛莉亚 海莉和我会在跳舞
and Gloria and Haley and I will still be dancing.
这只吗 一般都是乔帮她掖被子
This one? Joe tucks her in.
你怎么会知道
How would you know?
让你生气的新闻联播一结束
You go to bed right after
你就上床睡觉了
you get mad at the news.
对 你俩总是害我们玩得不够嗨
Yeah, it's you two that are keeping us down,
但今晚不会了
but not tonight.
今晚我们要出去好好耍一耍
Tonight, we are going out big.
没错
Oh, yeah!
对 你很时髦
Yes, you're very hip.
那是《古董巡展电视秀》的主题曲
That's the theme song to "The Antiques Roadshow."
他说得对
He's right.
好丢脸
That's embarrassing.
房子很棒吧
Great house, huh?
地理位置没的说
And you can't beat the location,
主要因为我就住在那
mainly 'cause I live right there.
我们很喜欢这房子
We love the house.
太好了
Great!
但我没法住在那座
But I could never live across the street
色情雕塑对面
from that pornographic statue.
我还真没注意到
I never noticed it.
是啊
Yeah.
你在屋里透过窗户就能看到
You could see it from inside when you look out the window.
我没有 你是说那个吗
Oh, I didn't -- uh, are you talking about that one?
真的很"大"
It's quite large.
我相信你
I'll take your word for it.
这栋房子已经挂牌两个月了
I've had this listing for two months,
但因为街对面那座雕塑 一直卖不出去
and I can't move it because of the statue across the street.
雕塑名叫《大理石和"硬木"》
It's called "Marble with Wood,"
这么说吧 雕塑完全是大理石做的
and let's just say it's made entirely of marble.
我们得想点办法 真的太淫秽了
We've got to do something about this. It's obscene.
《麦田守望者》刚出版的时候
That's what they said about "The Catcher in the Rye"
人们也都那么说
when it first came out.
你这是帮倒忙
You're not helping.
我们何不直接去敲那家的门
Why don't we just knock on the door
跟主人谈呢
and talk to him?
-我试过了 -那家伙是个混蛋
- I tried. - Yeah, the guy's a jerk.
我跟他说这对我们造成了多大的困扰
I told him how much it bothered us.
结果他好像很高兴
It only seemed to please him.
我说实话
I'm not gonna lie --
那雕塑让我对我的身材很不自信
It makes me feel bad about my body.
这害得我不放心让我的孩子在外面玩
I don't feel comfortable letting my kids play out here.
-是我们的孩子 -保罗 拜托
- Our kids. - Paul, please.
艺术是主观的 总有人会喜欢这种
Art is subjective. Some people would love this.
你们在聊什么呢
Hey what are you guys talking about?
他们来了
Here they come.
那座雕塑
The statue.
天呐 我们也很讨厌那玩意儿
Ohh, God, we hate that thing.
真的吗
You do?
当然了
Yeah.
我拼命赚钱可不是为了搬来
I didn't make my money to move to a neighborhood
街上有这种雕塑的社区
where they put something like that on the street.
色情作品应该在卧室的大电视里播放
Porn belongs on a big screen in the bedroom
或是浴室里的手机上
or your phone in the bathroom.
孩子们 去玩
Kids, go play.
要怎么办呢
Well...what are you gonna do?
看来我们只能习惯无视它了
Guess we'll just get used to ignoring it.
真希望他能做个
I just wish he was more concerned
-更好的邻居 -是啊
- with being a better neighbor. - Yeah.
阿门
Amen to that.
没错
Yeah.
我们正要去吃晚餐
Hey, we were just about to grab dinner.
你们想一起吗
You guys want to join us?
什么
What's that?
我说你们想去吃晚餐吗
I said, you guys want to go to dinner?
怎么
How's that?
如果你们不想去 那也没关系
If you guys don't want to, that's fine.
不不不不
No, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no. Oh, no, no, no.
-不不 -不
- No, no, no. - No.
你们是说不吗
A-are you saying no?
知道吗
You know what?
-当然行啦 -是啊
- Sure, why not? - Of course.
-好 -真棒
- All right! Great! - Great!
15分钟后门口见 我开车
We'll meet you out front. 15. I'll drive.
克莱尔 以防我们撞衫
Oh, Claire, just so our outfits don't clash,
我要穿蜥蜴纹哦
I'll be wearing lizard.
该死 我找件别的衣服
Ah, shoot. Well, I'll find something.
好
Okay.
这真讨喜啊 木瓶倒地的声音
Oh, don't you just love it -- the crash of the pins,
出租鞋喷雾的味道
the smell of the rental-shoe spray?
是啊 让我热血沸腾
Yeah, it does kind of get the blood going.
一个小细节
Oh, one small detail --
这是基佬保龄球联赛
This is an all-gay bowling league,
所以我跟大家说你是基佬
so I told everyone you're all gay.
什么
What?
你必须是基佬才能参赛
You have to be gay to play.
我们去跟大家见面吧
Let's go meet the guys.
算了 我不来了
Forget it. Not doing it.
杰 我们需要你
Jay, we need you.
没人会信我是基佬的
No one's gonna believe I'm gay.
为什么 因为你举止不够傲娇吗
Oh, why, because you're not flouncy enough?
杰 那很冒犯
Jay, that's offensive.
这世上有各种各样的基佬
There's all kinds of gays.
百老汇基佬 健身房基佬
You've got your broadway gays, your gym gays,
小鲜肉基佬 熊基佬 水獭基佬
your twinks, your bears, your otters,
妖孽型基佬
your "Hey, girl" Gays.
小狗基佬 幼兽基佬 白鲑基佬
You've got your pups, your cubs, your chubs.
最重要的是 有你这种
And most prominently, you've got your
"绝对看不出来是基佬"类型的基佬
average-joes-who-you-would never-know-are-gay gays.
水獭基佬是什么啊
What the hell is an otter?
20号赛道穿白裤子的
Lane 20. White pants.
你没必要改变自己的行为
Look, you don't have to do anything differently.
做自己就好 你就很基了
Just...be yourself. You're gay enough.
好啊 卡梅隆
Hello, Cameron.
我就觉得闻到了失败和廉价发胶的味道
I thought I smelled failure and cheap hair spray.
好啊 马丁 你气色不是太好
Oh, hello, Martin. You're looking unwell.
你能不能重复一下去年做过的事
Could you do that thing you did
那时候你输了
last year where you lose
想扔一把椅子
and then you try and throw a chair
但你没发现那把椅子是固定住的
but not realize it's bolted down
结果扭伤了背
and wrench your back
你还咒骂我
and then curse at me
而我对着你肥肥的红脸晃动着奖杯
while I wave a trophy in your big, red face, could you?
瞧瞧你 你好激动
Oh, boy, look at you. You're all worked up.
在乔安工艺品店
It must have been a tough day
做助理一定很累吧
assistant-managing that Jo-ann Fabrics.
是迈克尔工艺品店 你知道的 混蛋
It's a Michael's, and you know it, you son of a bitch!
好吧 我会参加 我不喜欢那个人
Fine. I'll do it. I don't like that guy.
但是如果我认识的人走了进来
But what happens if somebody I know comes in here
觉得我过着秘密生活怎么办
and thinks I'm living a secret life?
杰 相信我
Jay, trust me,
如果今晚有你认识的人走了进来
if someone you know comes in here tonight,
那他们才过着秘密生活
they're living a secret life.
-有道理 -跟大家见见面吧 各位
- You make a point. - Okay, let's meet the guys. Guys!
好啊 我好开心
Hey! I am in the best mood.
我的Uber司机长得酷似亚当·德利弗
My Uber driver looked just like Adam Driver.
你们准备好狂欢了吗
You guys ready to party?
-是的 出发 -去哪
- Yeah, let's go! - Where?
出去 我们走吧
Out. Let's do this.
才八点半 夜店再过一个小时才开门
It's 8:30. The doors don't even open for another hour.
那你来干什么
Well, then, what are you doing here?
热身
Pregame!
莫吉托和四海为家鸡尾酒
Mojitos and Cosmos --
你们两个种族的标志性酒水
the drinks of your peoples.
好吧 我们来狂欢
All right, let's get crazy.
我来切奶酪
I'll uncover the cheese.
我们十点半在夜店外和我的朋友们见面
So, we'll meet my friends outside the club at like 10:30.
是啊 乐队半夜才开始演出
Yeah, the band doesn't go on until midnight.
半夜
Midnight?
如果你们现在就听不见我说话
Okay, if you guys can't hear me now,
我们在吵闹的夜店可就有问题了
we're gonna have some real problems at the club.
-没问题 -我们没事 没事
- No problem. - No, we're good. We're good.
我希望30年以后也和你们一样酷
I hope I can be as cool as you guys in 30 years.
她觉得我们有50岁吗
Does she think we're 50?
不 她只是数学很差
No, no, she's just really bad at math.
连续两次全中
Two strikes in a row!
快找找出口吧
Familiarize yourself with the exit
某人简直势不可挡哟
because somebody's on fire!
杰 到你了
Okay, Jay, you're up.
好了 杰 我们去拿下第一个全中吧
All right, Jay. Let's get that first strike.
想着你会获得的奖赏
Keep your eye on the prize.
想象你今晚把那宝贝带回家
Imagine taking that bad boy home tonight.
杰瑞
Jerry...
抱歉 我今天有点不在状态
I'm sorry. I'm just off my game tonight.
你能行的
You got this.
你的新队员是谁
Who's your new guy?
他是我老公的叔叔
He's my husband's uncle.
你看起来很困惑
Oh, you look confused.
老公就是一个你不用给钱
A husband is somebody who loves you
就会爱你的人
that you don't have to pay.
该死
Damn it!
那个人不是基
That guy is not gay.
我可以取消你们的参赛资格
I could have you disqualified, you know.
他当然是基
Of course he's gay.
我不会弄错的
I'm never wrong.
我的基达可灵敏了
My gaydar is highly sensitive.
比如我现在就得离你远点
For instance, I have to move it away from you right now
免得被你闪瞎
before it explodes.
我会盯着杰叔叔的
I'm keeping an eye on uncle Jay.
-杰 -别担心 我会追上去的
- Okay, Jay -- - Don't worry. I'll pick up the spare.
不不不 有个更严重的问题
No, no, no, we got bigger problems.
马丁盯上我们了
Um... Martin's onto us.
你得表现得傲娇一点
You need to flounce it up a little bit.
但你不是说那样很冒犯人吗
But you said that was offensive, remember?
什么水獭和黄鼠狼之类的
The otters and weasels and stuff.
好吧 你知道什么更冒犯吗
Okay, you know what's more offensive?
让马丁赢
Martin winning.
所以你要表现出基佬的欢快气质来
So, we need to get you lighter in those rental loafers.
我哪里暴露了
What gave me away?
是因为我不够帅吗
I'm not handsome enough. Is that it?
很好 缺乏安全感又肤浅
Perfect. Insecure and superficial --
是个好的开始
It's a great start.
-要不要点瓶红酒 -好啊
- Should we order a bottle of wine? - Yes.
不用
Oh, no need.
罗尼从家里带了一瓶来
Ronnie brought this big daddy from home.
是的 盖[音同"喂"]
Yeah. Guy.
盖
Hey. Guy.
罗尼 他是有名字的
Oh, Ronnie, I'm sure he has a real name.
是啊 他就叫盖
Yeah, it's Guy.
拉方丹先生及太太 很高兴又见到你们
Mr. and Mrs. Lafontaine, so nice to see you again.
-你好 -我是盖 很高兴见到你们
- Hey, Guy. - Hi, I'm Guy. Pleasure.
-你好 盖 -你好
- Hi, Guy. - Hi.
好酒啊
Oh. Very nice.
2002年产的哈伦
2002 Harlan.
今晚要庆祝什么呢
What are we celebrating tonight?
我们终于有机会
Well, uh, we're finally having dinner
和邻居共进晚餐了
with our next-door neighbors.
你们的邻里关系一定很好
Well, you must be very good neighbors.
-真感谢你 -谢谢
- That's so nice. - Thank you.
这没什么
Oh, don't mention it.
很高兴能请你们来
It's nice to have you guys here.
孩子们都好吗
So, how are the kids?
好 就是气氛有点紧张
Uh, good. It's a little intense right now.
艾丽克斯正在纠结
Uh, Alex is freaking out about
到底去哪里上大学
where she's gonna go to college,
我们很担心她会去东海岸
and we're freaking out it's gonna be on the east coast.
是嘛 我们懂的
Oh, yeah. Well, we get that.
R.J.很快要去纽约
R.J.'s going to New York soon.
我觉得我到时会哭得
I think I'm gonna cry harder than the day
比我发现我怀他时还凶
I found out I was pregnant with him.
R.J.去纽约干什么啊
Yeah, what's R.J. got going on in New York?
我们想让他读商科
Well, we wanted him to go to college for business,
但他想玩音乐
but he wants to do his music.
所以 长话短说
So, long story short,
他要去茱莉亚音乐学院了
he's going to Juilliard.
茱莉亚音乐学院
Juilliard?
学钢琴
For piano.
其实主要是学作曲
Well, mostly for his composing.
这小子毛都没长齐
Kid can't hit the toilet,
但是每天脑子里都有新旋律
but he wakes up with symphonies in his head.
对啊
Right.
酒好了 你们想品一下吗
There we are. Would you like to taste?
-当然 -这瓶酒价值五百美金
- Oh, yeah. - That's a $500 bottle of wine.
相当于一百瓶你喝的那种酒
That's like 100 bottles of your wine.
很好 满上吧
Yeah, let 'er rip.
我准备好了
Oh, I'm ready!
该死
Damn it!
拜托 小卡 承认吧
Oh, come on, Cam. Admit it.
杰叔叔 不是基叔叔
Uncle Jay -- not gay.
天呐 你真是大错特错
Oh, my God. You could not be more wrong.
听我说
Look, okay.
如果他行为有点奇怪
If he's acting a little weird,
那是因为
it's just because...
他喜欢上你了
he totally likes you.
不 他才没有 他说了什么
No, he doesn't! What did he say?
好吧 听着 他不希望我说出来
Okay, look, he -- he -- he didn't want me to say anything
因为他很害羞
because he's shy.
所以他表现才那么奇怪
That's why he's being so awkward.
小卡 到你了
Cam, you're up.
到我了
I'm up.
我得走了
I got to go.
你好
Hey, there.
这杯是给你的
This is for you.
谢谢
Oh. Thanks.
而这个
And this...
是为了博君一笑
is for a little zing.
谁不爱笑呢
We do love zing.
马上回来
Be right back.
我等着
Be right here.
那人为什么对我这么好
Why is that guy being so nice to me?
今晚有点小变数
Well, there's been a-a new little twist in the evening.
我的啤酒也被变了 到底什么事
And now there's one in my beer. What's up?
我跟他说你看上他了
I told him you have a crush on him.
你干嘛要那么说
Why would you do that?
我没办法
I had no choice.
你把我骗到这里 让我装基佬
Well, you tricked me into coming here, you made me gay,
现在又多了个男朋友
now I have a boyfriend.
搞这些把戏就是为了那个奖杯吗
All these lies just to win a trophy?
对
Yes.
佩服 佩服
I respect that.
我朋友到了
Oh, those are my friends.
他们送手环来了
They're out front dropping off our wristbands.
大家都来...
What comes before part "B"?
开派对
Par-tay!
天呐 我忍了一个钟头了
Oh, my god. I've been holding that in for an hour.
歌洛莉亚 我做不到
Gloria, I'm not gonna make it.
不行也得去
You have to.
我们对杰和小卡夸下海口 要是不去
We talked so big to Cam and Jay that if we don't go out,
他们会取笑我们一辈子
they're never gonna let us live it down.
好吧
Okay.
或者就不去了吧
Or we could just blow it off, man.
别呀歌洛莉亚 起来
No, Gloria, come on, come on.
起来 起来 来来来
Get up, get up. Come on, come on, come on.
熬通宵是你的本性呢
Staying up all night -- it's in your blood.
你的家乡遍地是咖啡和可卡因呢
You come from the land of coffee and cocaine!
你也是啊 有谁比基友更爱跳舞
You too! Nobody likes to dance more than the gays.
假装你嗨了
Pretend you're on a float.
对 跳舞 好主意
Dancing. That's it. That's a good idea.
好 跳起来
Okay, dancing. Dancing.
我来放音乐
I'm gonna turn on some music here.
不错哦
This is good.
胳膊酸 跳不了"掀房顶"舞姿了
Oh, my "Raise the roof" elbow's a little sore.
这说明要下雨
Oh, yeah, that must mean rain.
天呐 你家小孩也是那副嘴脸啊
Oh, my god. Your kids give you that look, too?
是啊 我都记不得
Yeah, I swear I can't remember
他们的脸原来长啥样了
what their actual faces look like.
很有趣 对吧
This is fun. Isn't this fun?
今天聚在一起是因为我们
To think it just took us all hating the same statue
都讨厌那座雕塑
to bring us together.
要是人们有更多看不惯的东西世界会有多和谐
What a world it could be if people would just hate more.
是啊 到底该拿那雕塑怎么办
Yeah, what are we gonna do about that thing, huh?
这样不对啊 你都没办法工作了
It's not right that a guy like you can't even get his job done.
我们可以请愿
Well, we could start a petition.
可以去跟市议员说说
Yeah, or we could talk to our city councilman.
或者 这样如何
Or...how about this?
拿根绳子绑在那雕塑上
We take a rope, we tie it around the statue,
用我的卡车拉着
attach it to the back of my truck,
把那玩意拖到最近的垃圾场
and drag it to the nearest dump.
我喜欢
Love that.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
-我们不能那样做 -不能
- Uh, we can't do that. - No.
为什么不能 绳子我们有的是
Why not? We got tons of rope.
有没有绳子不是问题
Availability of rope isn't really the issue here.
这么做是破坏他人财物
It's -- it's destruction of property.
是违法的
It's against the law.
所以呢
So?
罗尼 这是文明社会
Ronnie, we live in a civilized society.
我们不是那种人
We're not those kinds of people, you know?
那你还
Says the lady who, uh,
用我的高档红酒来配鱼
paired my Cabernet with fish.
还需要什么吗
So, is there anything else I can get you?
不用 我们完事了
Nope. I think, uh, we've had enough.
这意味着两件事
And that means two things.
我还要喝的
I'm not done.
好耶 这音乐好棒
All right! Like the music!
你们真的很懂...
You guys really know h--
今晚发挥不好
I'm not getting good rotation tonight.
我可是被迷得团团转呢
Certainly made my head spin.
这要我说什么好
Oh, what can I say to that?
我能问你件事吗
Hey, can I ask you something?
你觉得这照片怎么样
What do you think of that picture?
一点都不像你
Doesn't look a thing like you.
我也是这么觉得
Exactly what I've been saying.
绝不是坐在我身旁的这个男人
Not the man sitting next to me.
沧桑帅气的脸
The rugged good looks...
宽阔的肩膀
...broad shoulders...
深邃的蓝眼睛
piercing blue eyes.
你就是凯文·科斯特纳
Hell, you're -- you're somewhere between
和查宁·塔图姆的混合体
Kevin Costner and Channing Tatum.
谁不想跟他俩混交呢
Who wouldn't want to be between them, huh?
杰 到你上场了
Okay, Jay, you're up.
谢谢 你的鼓励正是我需要的
Thank you, Martin. I needed that.
随时奉陪
Anytime.
这才是杰的水平呢
There's the real Jay!
你懂的
You know it!
宝宝在哪
Where is the baby?!
我起了 我起了
I'm up. I'm up.
你什么时候回来的
Hey, when did you get back?
一个小时前吧
Like an hour ago.
真的
Oh, really?
我在打夜店盹呢
I must have grabbed a little disco nap.
那是什么鬼
I don't know what that means.
你们确定要去吗
You sure you guys are up for this?
-当然啦 当然 -必须的
- Yeah, definitely, definitely. - Of course.
要不我们改天再去跳舞吧 比如说白天
Why don't we go dancing another time, like daytime?
我吃奶酪吃得好饱 要不...
Oh, you know, well, I'm pretty full of cheese, so --
不 不行
No, no.
如果我们现在不去
If we don't go out now,
就不是小卡和杰的"老"气在作怪了
this is not about Cam and Jay making us old,
而是我们真的老了
it means we are old.
这是自尊心的问题
This is about pride.
我们必须证明我们还是可以出去浪和嗨的
We need to prove that we can still go out and have fun.
你懂我的意思吗 米奇
Are you with me, Mitch?
懂
Yes!
-我懂 -那就好
- Yes, I am! - Okay.
-我们走起吧 -好
- All right, let's go. - Okay.
路上能买杯咖啡吗
Can we get some coffee on the way?
-不能喝咖啡 -不喝咖啡
- No coffee! - No coffee!
太棒了 宝贝
Oh, yes, baby!
我们队终于找到最好的状态了
Our team had really found its groove.
我们很快打败了
We quickly eliminated
围兜队和洋娃娃球道队
The Pinafores and Alley Of The Dolls,
来到与我死对头球队的最终对决
putting us in the finals against my archrival.
就像红袜队和洋基队 阿里和弗雷泽
In the tradition of Red Sox/Yankees, Ali/Frazier,
一切终归于
it all came down to
"小闲闲布兰妮"对阵"马丁和基佬们"
The Britney Spares vs. Martin And His Merry Men.
紧张局面一触即发
The tension was building...
谁能在我吃光这些薯条之前
Could somebody please take these fries
把它们拿走
before I eat them all?
情绪逐渐高涨
... and emotions were running high.
那个 杰 我想说
Um, so, Jay, I just, um
我想说不管待会儿怎么样
I just wanted to say that whatever happens,
我都 很高兴认识你
it was, uh, r-really nice meeting you.
也很高兴认识你 马丁
Well, you too, Martin.
我在想 那什么
Uh, d-do -- wondering, I don't know,
你 你愿不愿意改天一起吃个饭
w-w-would you like to have dinner sometime
或者出去逛逛 或者
or maybe hang out or,
-之类的 -我的天 你知道吗
- or something like that? - Oh, geez. You know what,
我 我真的受宠若惊
I'm, I'm, I'm really, really flattered
我明白了
Okay, I get it.
-不 不是 -没事 我完全理解
- No, no, it's not. - No, no, I get it, totally.
真的没事 我懂的
No, it's okay. I understand.
非常感谢你 祝你好运
Thank you very much! Good luck!
然后就这样 马丁被瓦解了
And just like that, Martin fell apart.
到了最后一格 完全要看杰的发挥
By the last frame, it was all up to Jay.
杰 我们只要再击倒六个球瓶就行了
Okay, Jay, we only need six pins!
六个有多了 各位
I don't think it's gonna be six, guys.
我们赢了 我们赢了
We won! We won!
这是我人生中第五幸福的时刻
This is the fifth-happiest moment of my life!
收养莉莉 和米奇尔结婚
Adopting Lily, marrying Mitchell,
中学橄榄球赛冠军
high-school football championship,
看《魔法坏女巫》的时候坐在
and sitting behind Sarah Jessica Parker
萨拉·杰茜卡·帕克后面
at "Wicked."
来了
All right!
好耶
Okay!
一起来 一起嗨 一起来嗨
Let's do this! Let's do this! Let's do this!
我办不到
I can't do this.
我也不行
Me either.
我们快50了
Ah! We're almost 50!
回家的路 尽管距离不到一英里
The ride home, while less than a mile long,
却如此地漫长
was interminable.
晚餐时建立起来的友谊
Whatever bridges had been built
都破碎了[烧糊了]
were burned,
就像我的鱼
like my fish was,
所以说吃鱼配红酒也不是...
which is why red wine was a --
亲爱的 你没必要为自己解释什么
Hey, honey, you don't have to defend yourself.
只要一喝酒 这女人就分不清青红皂白
When it comes to wine, this woman doesn't see color.
你在她面前放什么 她都会喝
She'll drink whatever's put in front of her.
这下好了
Oh, great.
他们还打了灯光
They put lights on it.
停车
Stop the car.
我们必须处理掉那东西 他们说得对
We have to tear that thing down. They're right.
那是唯一的解决办法
It's the only way.
-什么 -这才像话
- What? - Now you're talking!
这才是那个
There's the girl
时不时出现在我春梦里的女孩
that I occasionally have sex dreams about.
对 那是真的 他告诉过我
Yeah, that's true. He told me.
-不 不 这太疯狂了 -说得对
- No, no, no. This is crazy. - Yes.
-别这么做 -你还想再等多少个月
- Don't do this. - How many months do you want to spend
去走那些政府的繁文缛节
trying to fight through some bureaucratic red tape
让他们把那玩意儿给拆掉
to get that thing taken down
-最后被告知我们什么也做不了 -不
- only to be told there's nothing we can do? - Oh, no.
待在车上
Stay in the car.
Stay in the car!
-我们怎么弄 -拿着这个 绕过去
- What do we do? - Here, take that. Put it around.
-穿个圈 -好 我来
- Through the loop. - Yeah, I do this.
系好了
Tie it down.
不够长 我把车往后倒一点
It's too short. I got to back the truck up.
不 不行
No! No!
菲尔 你在干嘛 赶紧的 开门
Phil, what are you doing? Come on. Open the door.
-我不能让这事发生 -拜托 伙计
- I can't allow this to happen! - Come on, man.
我是这个社区里有头有脸的一份子
I'm a respected member of the community!
我的广告都登在公交车座上了
I'm on bus benches!
-你也太守规矩了 -开门 快开门
- You're such a boy scout! - Open the door. Open the door.
我想要拆掉那玩意儿的心跟你们一样
I want that thing gone as much as anyone,
但不能以这种方式
but not like this.
我要把这辆卡车开走
I'm gonna take this truck.
我要去吃点酸奶冰淇淋
I'm gonna go get some fro-yo.
我建议你们走回家 顺便冷静一下
I suggest you use the walk home to calm down.
一旦冷静下来 你们会感谢我的
Once you have, you're gonna thank me.
菲尔 老天 你在倒车...
Phil. Oh, my god! You're going back...
谢谢你
Thank you!
我以为是前进挡
I thought I was in drive!
菲尔
Phil!
我们今晚太棒了 伙计们
We were awesome tonight, guys.
你觉得我们可以挑战拉拉了吗
Do you think we're good enough to take on the lesbians?
天呐 不能
Oh, god, no.
我请大家再喝一轮
One more round on me.
打得好 马丁
Good match, Martin.
你也是 杰 恭喜你
You too, Jay. Congratulations.
谢谢 希望我没有让你失去信心
Thanks. I hope I didn't throw off your game at all.
不 都是我 我总是那样
No. That's all me. I do that.
我总会好高骛远
I get ahead of myself.
制造了期望 越堆越高
Create expectations, build them up.
不用担心我 我会去找个人生导师
Don't worry about me. I'm going to see a life coach.
一切都会改变
It is going to change everything.
听着 今晚我的状态并不好
Well, listen, I wasn't feeling great about myself tonight,
是你帮我摆脱了恐惧
and you helped get me out of that funk.
我不应该这样
And it wouldn't be right
任由你难过下去
for me to let you leave feeling bad.
你是个好人
You're a great guy,
我拒绝你的原因是...
and the reason I turned you down is because...
要大声说出来比我想得要难得多
It's much harder to say out loud than I thought.
我...
I'm...
我不是同性恋
I'm not gay.
你是直男吗
You're straight?
是谁 发生什么事了
Who's what? What's happening?
终于可以说出来了 感觉太好了
Whoa, it feels good to finally tell someone.
四个小时了
For four hours,
我一直害怕会被别人发现
I've been living in fear that I'd be found out.
你们知道那种感觉是怎样的吗
Do you have any idea what that feels like?
好吧
Right.
杰 谢谢你承认了
Jay, thank you for admitting that.
你真是个正直的人
You are a real class act.
取消资格
Disqualified!
你们输了
You lose!
给我 那是我的 老天呐
Give me that! That's mine! Oh, my god!
天呐 冠军
Oh, my god, champions!
我们又是冠军了
We're champions again!
-让我出去 -天呐
- Let me out! - Oh, my god!
你猜怎么着 杰
Guess what, Jay.
你是我新的死对头
You're my new archrival.
我觉得很糟
I feel terrible.
-你太守规矩了 童子军 -是啊
- You're too good, boy scout. - Yeah.
所以你才需要有我们这样的人在身边
That's why you need people like us around.
承认吧 你很高兴看到那玩意儿被毁了
Admit it -- you're happy it's gone.
我很高兴
I'm happy it's gone,
不过很奇怪 我们都坐在外面
but it's weird we're out here
而不是关着灯躲在屋里面
instead of inside with the lights off.
这就叫做欲盖弥彰
It's called hiding in plain sight.
我们就坐在这里表现出胸怀坦荡的样子
We just sit here and act like we got nothing to hide,
他们就不会怀疑我们
and they won't suspect a thing.
各位 我要问你们几个问题
Folks, I need to ask you a couple of questions.
有人说他们听见有辆卡车把雕塑撞倒了
Someone said they heard a big truck run over that statue.
什么 我们什么也不知道
What? Well, we wouldn't know anything about that
我们刚才在外面吃晚餐
because we were at dinner.
介意我看一下你的卡车吗
Mind if I take a look at your truck?
你好 巴迪[伙计]
Hey, Buddy.
别管警察叫伙计 他们讨厌那样
Oh, don't call a cop "Buddy." They hate that.
不 那是他的名字
No, that's his name.
我卖过他一套公寓
I sold him a condo.
-菲尔 -是我 巴迪
- Phil? - Yeah, Buddy.
我们四个刚才在吃晚餐 我可以担保
The four of us were at dinner. I can vouch for it.
如果你要找罪人的话
If you're looking to solve a crime,
这位女士吃鱼配红酒
this one here had red wine with fish.
是我干的 没错
Oh, I did. I did.
抱歉打扰你们了 祝你们今晚过得愉快
Sorry to bother you. You folks have a good night.
你也是
You too.
我再也不是童子军了
No more boy scout.
看来今晚你要跟亡命之徒一起睡了
Looks like you're sleeping with an outlaw tonight.
是啊
Yes.
我们也加入
Uh, we're in.
-不 我在跟克莱尔说话 -是的
- No, no, I was talking to Claire. - Yeah.
你是说你们对我们没兴趣吗
Are you saying you're not attracted to us?
-没有 没有 -没有 没有
- No, no, no... - No, no, no...
-没有 -没有
- No. - No.
真不可思议
It's unbelievable.
爸妈居然在跟他们
Mom and dad are sitting outside
以前很讨厌的邻居一起坐在外面
with the neighbors they used to hate
谈天说地 就像他们是最好的朋友似的
yukking it up like they're all best friends.
为什么呢
And why?
因为有酒吗
Because there's wine?
不 因为艺术
No. Because of art.
那个雕塑太令人不悦了
That statue that was so offensive
引发了他们的话题
provoked a conversation.
那就是艺术的力量 会使人凝聚起来
That's what art does. It brings people together.
即使很恶心也行吗
Even if it's gross?
有人觉得恶心 可有人觉得美丽
One person's gross is another person's beautiful.
那真的很强大
Wow. That's really powerful.
你认为这也可以让人们凝聚起来吗
Do you think this could bring people together?
这是我老二的自画像
It's a self-portrait of... my junk.
不许再跟我说话
Never speak to me again.
伪君子
Hypocrite.